Sergey Hmurovich

Front-end developer

CONTACTS













<u>Minsk, Belarus</u>



+375297374777



ksn_i777@mail.ru

SKILLS



React

library for building user interfaces



Redux / Redux Toolkit state container for applications



TypeScript

strongly typed language based on JS



JavaScript

language for web application interactivity



application programming interface



development application through testing

Storybook environment for developing a library of UI



application version control system



Material-UI

library of components for the UI



HTML5 document markup language

document style language



SCSS / SASS

CSS-based metalanguage



_. English

A2 in progress

ABOUT ME

I'm a front-end developer with experience developing the visible part of web applications. The main technologies of my work are React, Redux and TypeScript. Every day I improve my skills in this direction and plan to expand them with new technologies, such as Angular and Vue. I'm always open to offers. Tell me more about your needs.

PROJECTS

CARDS - Word learning application

stack: React, Redux Toolkit, TS, Axios, Formik, MUI, SASS

TODOLIST - Task manager

stack: React, Redux Toolkit, TS, Axios, Formik, MUI, TDD

SOCIAL NETWORK - Online platform for communication

stack: React, Redux, TS, Axios, Redux-form

EXPERIENCE

2022 - present / Part-time Front-end developer

03.2019 - 01.2023 / Full-time Head of design sector

03.2014 - 02.2019 / Full-time Design engineer

EDUCATION

2022 / IT-INCUBATOR / Front-end developer (React, Redux, TS, JS, Rest API, TDD) 2009 - 2015 / A.D.Sakharov ISEU / Nuclear and radiation safety engineer